tennisrecruiting.net 2015-06-09

# The Tennis Recruiting Network

| 

Your privacy is important to Sirius Software, Inc. and TennisRecruiting.net ("TennisRecruiting"). This Privacy Policy defines privacy aspects specific to the TennisRecruiting.net Website and affiliated websites owned by TennisRecruiting and its subsidiaries. TennisRecruiting has created this policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This statement describes the information practices at TennisRecruiting websites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. 

**CONSENT**

Your use of the TennisRecruiting.net Website signifies your consent to us collecting personal information about you in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**MINORS**

TennisRecruiting encourages parents and guardians to monitor and participate in their children's online activities. Although this is a website directed at junior tennis players and their families, we do not knowingly collect information from our guests under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, do not send any information about yourself to TennisRecruiting. USERS UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE ARE NOT PERMITTED TO REGISTER AT TENNISRECRUITING.NET. If TennisRecruiting discovers that a child under the age of 13 has provided TennisRecruiting with personal information, we will delete the child’s personal information from our system. Information for a child under 13 years of age can only be submitted by a parent or legal guardian. TennisRecruiting will ask you to indicate your age to verify compliance with these policies.

All information we collect is in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.). 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

In general, you can visit TennisRecruiting.net on the Internet without telling us who you are or giving any personal information about yourself. There are times, however, when we or our partners may need information from you. 

You may choose to give us personal information in a variety of situations. For example, you may want to give us information, such as your name and address or e-mail id, to correspond with you, to process an order, or to provide you with a subscription. We intend to let you know how we will use such information before we collect it from you. If you give us personal information about somebody else, such as a spouse or relative, we will assume that you have their permission to do so. 

**USING AND SHARING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

The following paragraphs describe in more detail how TennisRecruiting may use your personal information and with whom we may share it. Depending on the area of TennisRecruiting.net you are visiting, one or more of the paragraphs may apply. For example, if you order a product from TennisRecruiting, your information will be handled as described in such paragraphs as Fulfilling Your Transaction Request and Marketing Use. 

**FULFILLING YOUR TRANSACTION REQUEST**

If you request something from the TennisRecruiting.net Website, for example, a product or service, a callback, or specific marketing materials, we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. To help us do this, we may share information, with others, for instance, TennisRecruiting's business partners, financial institutions, shipping companies, postal or government authorities (for example, Customs authorities) involved in fulfillment. In connection with a transaction we may also contact you as part of our customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes. 

**MARKETING USE**

The information you provide at the TennisRecruiting.net Website may also be used by TennisRecruiting or its affiliates for marketing and promotional purposes. However, TennisRecruiting will not sell or lease your information to third-parties, partners, or sponsors.

**DISCUSSION FORUMS AND CHAT ROOMS**

If you participate in a TennisRecruiting.net discussion forum or chat room, you should be aware that the information you provide there will be made broadly available to others, potentially inside or outside TennisRecruiting.net, who have access to that discussion forum or chat room. Also, please recognize that individual forums and chat rooms may have additional rules and conditions. Each participant's opinion on a forum or chat room is his or her own and should not be considered as reflecting the opinion of TennisRecruiting. 

**CONTESTS, SWEEPSTAKES, AND SURVEYS**

From time to time, TennisRecruiting.net may offer you the option to participate in contests, sweepstakes, or surveys. If you would like to participate, we may ask you for contact information, preferences, or other information. This information may be used to conduct research, improve our offerings, or award prizes. Our contests and sweepstakes may have separate rules and we will identify how the information that you supply will be used in each case. 

**INFORMATION SECURITY AND QUALITY**

We intend to protect your personal information and to maintain its quality. We implement appropriate measures and processes, such as using encryption when transmitting certain sensitive information, to help us to keep your information secure and to maintain its quality. 

**SUPPLEMENTING INFORMATION**

From time to time we may supplement information you give us via the TennisRecruiting.net Website with information from other sources, such as information validating your address or other available information about businesses. This is to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect and to help us provide a better service. 

**COOKIES**

We sometimes collect non-identifiable information from visits to our websites to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit, and we also measure visitor activity on the TennisRecruiting.net Websites, but we do so in ways that keep the information non-identifiable. This information is sometimes known as "clickstream data." TennisRecruiting, or others on behalf of TennisRecruiting may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service. 

Also, when we collect personal data from you in a transaction, we may extract some information about that transaction in a non-identifiable format and combine it with other non-identifiable information such as clickstream data. This information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. This information is not reviewed at an individual level. If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner you can disable your cookies. 

We collect the information we mentioned in the previous paragraphs through the use of various technologies, including one called "cookies". A cookie is a piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer but not you. Some TennisRecruiting.net pages use cookies, sent by TennisRecruiting.net or its third party vendors, or other technologies to better serve you when you return to the Website. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some websites may not work properly. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

**IP ADDRESS**

TennisRecruiting.net uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Website. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. 

**SERVICE QUALITY MONITORING**

Certain Web transactions may also involve you calling us or our calling you. Please be aware that it is the general practice of TennisRecruiting to monitor and in some cases record such calls for staff training or quality assurance purposes. 

**DISCLOSURES REQUIRED BY LAW**

Please be aware that in certain circumstances, it is possible that personal information may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders. 

**PRIVACY TECHNOLOGY**

Technology will increasingly help give you more control over your personal information. It will also help organizations to manage their privacy practices and policies. 

Products and services are available which can assist you with the control of your personal information while navigating the Web. See the Online Privacy Alliance website for an overview of many privacy-related tools. Please note that TennisRecruiting has not formally evaluated these tools. 

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

TennisRecruiting.net Websites may contain links to other websites. TennisRecruiting is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those other websites. 

**SUBMISSIONS**

With the exception of credit card numbers for the purchase of products and services, TennisRecruiting does not want to receive confidential or proprietary information through the TennisRecruiting.net website. 

TennisRecruiting collects player information including, but not limited to, graduation year, high school, tennis academy, handedness, career highlights, academic information, and contact information. This player information is clearly divided into public information ("Public Information") and private information ("Private Information"). TennisRecruiting will display Public Information at TennisRecruiting.net and affiliate sites for the general public. Private Information will only be made available to college tennis coaches.

All other information sent to TennisRecruiting with the exception of credit card numbers, will be deemed NOT CONFIDENTIAL. You grant TennisRecruiting an unrestricted, irrevocable license to display, use, modify, perform, reproduce, transmit, and distribute any information you send TennisRecruiting for any and all commercial and non-commercial purposes. 

TennisRecruiting may, but is not obligated to, review or monitor areas on its site where users may transmit or post information and data. TennisRecruiting is not responsible for the accuracy of any information and data. 

You are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from this web site any libelous, obscene, defamatory, pornographic, or other materials that would violate any laws. However, if such communications do occur, TennisRecruiting will have no liability related to the content of any such communications. 

**PROTECTING YOURSELF WHILE ONLINE**

You can help to protect your information by safeguarding your TennisRecruiting.net user name and password. 

**CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

TennisRecruiting reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check back periodically to be familiar with our terms, especially before you provide any personally identifiable information. 

**CONTACTING TENNISRECRUITING**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website or your dealings with this Website, contact: 

Security Department   
TennisRecruiting.net   
P. O. Box 71912   
Marietta, GA 30007-1912   

| 

| [](http://www.facebook.com/TennisRecruiting) | BECOME A FAN  
---|---  
  
[](http://www.facebook.com/TennisRecruiting)   Help build our following.   [Follow us on Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/TennisRecruiting)

RECENT COMMITMENTS 

[](http://tennisexpress.7eer.net/c/67286/124234/2591?sharedid=proLogo&subId2=0&subId3=ROS&u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tennisexpress.com)|  WTA GEAR - SHOES   
---|---  
  
[](http://tennisexpress.7eer.net/c/67286/124234/2591?sharedid=proSmall&subId1=Sabine+Lisicki&subId2=0&subId3=ROS&u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww%2Etennisexpress%2Ecom%2Fcategory%2Ecfm%2Ftennis%2Fsabine%2Dlisicki%2Dtennis%2Dpro) |   |  **Sabine Lisicki** [NIKE Women's Zoom Vapor 9.5 Tour Tennis Shoes](http://tennisexpress.7eer.net/c/67286/124234/2591?sharedid=proGear&subId1=Sabine+Lisicki&subId2=0&subId3=ROS&u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww%2Etennisexpress%2Ecom%2Fnike%2Dwomens%2Dzoom%2Dvapor%2D95%2Dtour%2Dtennis%2Dshoes%2Dfuchsia%2Dglow%2Dand%2Ddove%2Dgray%2D44148)  
Buy Now: $135.00  
---|---|---  
[](http://tennisexpress.7eer.net/c/67286/124234/2591?sharedid=proSmall&subId1=Sorana+Cirstea&subId2=0&subId3=ROS&u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww%2Etennisexpress%2Ecom%2Fcategory%2Ecfm%2Ftennis%2Fsorana%2Dcirstea) |   |  **Sorana Cirstea** [adidas Women's Stella McCartney Barricade Tennis Shoes](http://tennisexpress.7eer.net/c/67286/124234/2591?sharedid=proGear&subId1=Sorana+Cirstea&subId2=0&subId3=ROS&u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww%2Etennisexpress%2Ecom%2Fadidas%2Dwomens%2Dstella%2Dmccartney%2Dbarricade%2Dtennis%2Dshoes%2Dcore%2Dwhite%2Dand%2Dsake%2D39373)  
Was: $125.00   **Now: $74.95**  
[](http://tennisexpress.7eer.net/c/67286/124234/2591?sharedid=proSmall&subId1=Nadia+Petrova&subId2=0&subId3=ROS&u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww%2Etennisexpress%2Ecom%2Fcategory%2Ecfm%2Ftennis%2FNadia%2DPetrova%2Dtennis%2Dpro) |   |  **Nadia Petrova** [BABOLAT Women's SFX White Tennis Shoes](http://tennisexpress.7eer.net/c/67286/124234/2591?sharedid=proGear&subId1=Nadia+Petrova&subId2=0&subId3=ROS&u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww%2Etennisexpress%2Ecom%2Fbabolat%2Dwomens%2Dsfx%2Dwhite%2Dtennis%2Dshoes%2Dwhitegrey%2D26416)  
Buy Now: $99.95  
[](http://tennisexpress.7eer.net/c/67286/124234/2591?sharedid=proSmall&subId1=Barbora+Strycova&subId2=0&subId3=ROS&u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww%2Etennisexpress%2Ecom%2Fcategory%2Ecfm%2Ftennis%2Fbarbora%2Dstrycova%2Dtennis%2Dpro) |   |  **Barbora Strycova** [NIKE Women's Zoom Vapor 9.5 Tour Tennis Shoes](http://tennisexpress.7eer.net/c/67286/124234/2591?sharedid=proGear&subId1=Barbora+Strycova&subId2=0&subId3=ROS&u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww%2Etennisexpress%2Ecom%2Fnike%2Dwomens%2Dzoom%2Dvapor%2D95%2Dtour%2Dtennis%2Dshoes%2Dfuchsia%2Dglow%2Dand%2Ddove%2Dgray%2D44148)  
Buy Now: $135.00  

ITA NEWS

A quick interview with ATA's Karim Hossam before he heads off to Florida to play in the Orange Bowl in Florida.

THE LATEST FROM ZOOTENNIS
